Guide to the Beyond the Pale Records TAM.718
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Andy Stettner on Diallo Trial; Larry Cohler-Esses on Daycare Voucher Scandal; Melvin Jules Bukiet on Neurotica [2000-067], 2000-02-13; cuid34068 (Box 14, Audiocassette 718_0503)
  Duration: 1:03:23, Preservation Note: Digital Errors and Dropouts During Program; Program in Silence from 04:28 to 26:07, 26:59 to 27:58, and from 32:53 to 36:05; Clicks and Pops During Program
- Jerome Siegel on Rabbis' Letter; Michel Warschawski on Jerusalem; Megan Ortiz on Diallo Trial; David Espar on Lost Tribes of Israel [2000-068], 2000-02-20; cuid34069 (Box 14, Audiocassette 718_0504)
- Andy Stettner on Diallo Verdict; Emily Bilski on Berlin Metropolis Exhibition at the Jewish Museum; Ruth Messinger on AJWS Project for Women in Afghanistan [2000-18], 2000-02-27; cuid34070 (Box 8, Audiocassette 718_0281)
  Duration: 0:57:45, Preservation Note: Side B is Blank; Program Distorted at Times; Static During Program
  Duplicate of 718_0287, 718_0513
- A: Andy Stettner on Diallo Verdict; Ruth Messinger on AJWS Project for Women in Afghanistan / B: Peretz Kidron at the Jerusalem: A City of Two People's Festival; Human Rights Watch Film Festival with Nurit Kedar [2000-24], 2000 February 27; 2000 June 18; cuid34071 (Box 9, Audiocassette 718_0287)
  Duration: 1:57:33, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times
  Duplicate of 718_0281, 718_0513
- Andy Stettner on Diallo Verdict; Emily Bilski on Berlin Metropolis Exhibition at the Jewish Museum; Karl Heinz Muller on Kurt Weill's The Eternal Road; Ruth Messinger on Educating Girls Under the Taliban [2000-077], 2000-02-27; cuid34072 (Box 14, Audiocassette 718_0513)
  Duration: 0:57:52, Preservation Note: Digital Errors During Program; Program Distorted at Times
  Duplicate of 718_0281, 718_0287
- A: Emma Lazarus / B: John Brown 2000 with Matt Meyer, Laura Whitehorn, and Paul Buhle; Workmen's Circle 110th Anniversary with Nancy Sinkoff and Mark Mlotek; JFREJ Mock Bet Din [2000-002], 2000 March 5; 2000 May 7; cuid34073 (Box 8, Audiocassette 718_0265)
  Duration: 2:01:05, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; High Background Noise During Program; Speed Fluctuations During Program
  Duplicate of 718_0282, 718_0491, 718_1003
- A: Emma Lazarus / B: John Brown 2000; Workmen's Circle Anniversary [2000-19], 2000 March 5; 2000 May 7; cuid34074 (Box 9, Audiocassette 718_0282)
  Duration: 2:01:58, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; Static During Program; Program Recorded at a Very High Level; Dropouts During Program
  Duplicate of 718_0265, 718_0491, 718_1003
- Emma Lazarus with Nan Rubin [2000-055], 2000-03-05; cuid34075 (Box 14, Audiocassette 718_0491)
  Duration: 1:00:54, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; Digital Errors During Program
  Duplicate of 718_0265, 718_0282, 718_1003
- Emma Lazarus [2000-088-z], 2000-03-05; cuid34076 (Box 34, Reel 718_1003)
  Duration: 0:48:00, Preservation Note: Broken Splices Repaired; Static During Program; Program Distorted at Times
  Duplicate of 718_0265, 718_0282, 718_0491
- A: Richie Perez and Ron Daniels on Police Policy after Diallo; Irving/Lipstadt Holocaust Denial Libel Trial / B: Arthur Strimling on Letter from Rudy Giuliani; Bob Hughes and Norm Fruchter on CFE trial; Tony Kushner Purimspiel; Richard Goldstein on Hans Haacke [2000-001], 2000 March 12; 2000 March 20; cuid34077 (Box 8, Audiocassette 718_0264)
  Duration: 2:01:01, Preservation Note: High Background Noise During Program; Program Distorted at Times; High Amount of Buzz During Program; Static During Program
  Duplicate of 718_0482, 718_0488
- Irving/Lipstadt Holocaust Denial Libel Trial; Police Brutality and Actions [2000-052], 2000-03-12; cuid34078 (Box 14, Audiocassette 718_0488)
  Duration: 1:01:10, Preservation Note: Digital Errors During Program; Channel Imbalance from 37:57 to 41:58; Static During Program
  Duplicate of 718_0264
- A: Joan Lum, Raquel Grande, Basia Makowska on "Ain't I a Woman?" Conference; Jimmy Allen and Professor Leon Litwack on Without Sanctuary: Lynching Photography in America Exhibition / B: Rabbi Liever on Reform Movement Stance on Gay Marriage; Barbara Bowen on Spring PSC-CUNY Elections; Stanley Aronowitz on The Knowledge Factory; Cindy Greenberg on April 15 Demonstration after Diallo Verdict [2000-13], 2000 March 13; 2000 April 2; cuid34079 (Box 8, Audiocassette 718_0276)
  Duration: 2:00:07, Preservation Note: Channel Imbalance; Program Distorted at Times; Static During Program; Brief Speed Fluctuation at End of Side A During Program
  Duplicate of 718_0283, 718_0483
- Purim Show; Rich Goldstein on Hans Haacke at Whitney [2000-046], 2000-03-19; cuid34080 (Box 13, Audiocassette 718_0482)
  Duration: 0:59:20, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; Digital Errors During Program
- A: "Ain't I a Woman?" Conference / B: Rabbi Liever on Reform Movement Stance on Gay Marriage [2000-20], 2000 March 26; 2000 April 2; cuid34081 (Box 9, Audiocassette 718_0283)
  Duration: 2:01:46, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times
  Duplicate of 718_0276, 718_0483
- "Ain't I a Woman?" Conference; Without Sanctuary: Lynching Photography in America Exhibition [2000-053], 2000-03-26; cuid34082 (Box 14, Audiocassette 718_0489)
- Reform Movement Stance on Gay Marriage; CUNY Union Elections; Stanley Aronowitz on The Knowledge Factory Book; Cindy Greenberg on Police Brutality Protest (Partial) [2000-047], 2000-04-02; cuid34083 (Box 13, Audiocassette 718_0483)
  Duration: 0:44:14, Preservation Note: Digital Errors During Program; Program Distorted at Times
  Duplicate of 718_0276, 718_0283
- A: 25th Anniversary of Vietnam Peace / B: Ziad Abbas, Amy Goodman [2000-007], 2000 April 16; 2000 April 23; cuid34084 (Box 8, Audiocassette 718_0270)
  Duration: 1:59:47, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; Crosstalk During Program
  Duplicate of 718_0273, 718_0512
- A: Update on Palestinian Refugees with Ziad Abbas; Live Report from IMF/World Bank Demonstrations with Amy Goodman; Seder Readings by Ellen Lippmann, Michael Lerner, et al. / B: Leslie Cagan, 25th anniversary of the Peace in Vietnam; U.S. Holocaust Memorial Museum Symposium on Nazis and Homosexuals with Peter Black; Shapiro and Smith Dance Performance at Symphony Space with Daniel Shapiro [2000-10], 2000 April 16; 2000 April 23; cuid34085 (Box 8, Audiocassette 718_0273)
  Duration: 1:59:50, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; Static During Program
  Duplicate of 718_0270, 718_0512
- Marathon Special, Adrienne Cooper, Ghetto Tango, Part 3 [2000-004], 2000-04-21; cuid34086 (Box 8, Audiocassette 718_0267)
  Duration: 0:38:04, Preservation Note: Side B is Blank
  Duplicate of 718_0269, 718_0295, 718_0493, 718_0494, 718_0495
- U.S. Holocaust Memorial Museum Symposium on Nazis and Homosexuals with Peter Black; Shapiro and Smith Dance Performance at Symphony Space with Daniel Shapiro [2000-076], 2000-04-23; cuid34087 (Box 14, Audiocassette 718_0512)
  Duration: 1:03:54, Preservation Note: Digital Errors During Program; Program in Silence from 49:28 to 50:35; Program Distorted at Times
  Duplicate of 718_0270, 718_0273
- A: "Mission Impossible" Youth Theater Performance; Holocaust Reparations for the Roma / B: Marathon: Theater in Holocaust [2000-003], 2000 April 30; 2000 May 21; cuid34088 (Box 8, Audiocassette 718_0266)
  Duration: 1:01:18, Preservation Note: Side B is Blank; Program Distorted at Times
  Related to 718_0267, 718_0269, 718_0295, 718_0493, 718_0494, 718_0495
- "Mission Impossible" Youth Theater Performance; Holocaust Reparations for the Roma [2000-80-z], 2000-04-30; cuid34089 (Box 13, Audiocassette 718_0468)
  Duration: 1:02:29, Preservation Note: Digital Errors During Program; Program Distorted at Times
- JFREJ Mock Bet Din; John Brown 2000; Workmen's Circle 100th Anniversary [2000-056], 2000-05-07; cuid34090 (Box 14, Audiocassette 718_0492)
  Duration: 1:00:22, Preservation Note: Digital Errors During Program; Program Distorted at Times
  Duplicate of 718_0265, 718_0282, 718_0491, 718_1003
- Marathon, Parts 2 and 3 (Partial) [2000-0056], 2000-05-21; cuid34091 (Box 8, Audiocassette 718_0269)
  Duration: 1:47:08, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; High Frequency Background Noise During Program
  Duplicate of 718_0267, 718_0295, 718_0493, 718_0494, 718_0495
- Marathon, Adrienne Cooper, Ghetto Tango, Parts 2 of 3 [2000-032], 2000-05-21; cuid34092 (Box 9, Audiocassette 718_0295)
  Duration: 1:07:41, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times
  Duplicate of 718_0267, 718_0269, 718_0493, 718_0494, 718_0495
- Marathon Special: Ghetto Tango, Theatrical Performance During the Holocaust, Part 1 [2000-057], 2000-05-21; cuid34093 (Box 14, Audiocassette 718_0493)
  Duration: 1:00:01
  Duplicate of 718_0267, 718_0269, 718_0295, 718_0494, 718_0495
- Marathon Special: Ghetto Tango, Theatrical Performance During the Holocaust, Part 2 (Partial) [2000-058], 2000-05-21; cuid34094 (Box 14, Audiocassette 718_0494)
  Duration: 1:07:02
  Duplicate of 718_0267, 718_0269, 718_0295, 718_0493, 718_0495
- Marathon Special: Ghetto Tango, Theatrical Performance During the Holocaust, Part 3 (Partial) [2000-059], 2000-05-21; cuid34095 (Box 14, Audiocassette 718_0495)
  Duration: 0:37:51, Preservation Note: Digital Errors During Program
  Duplicate of 718_0267, 718_0269, 718_0295, 718_0493, 718_0494
- Israel Withdraws from Lebanon; Alice Mattison on The Book Borrower; Scottsboro Boys Documentary [2000-051], 2000-05-28; cuid34096 (Box 14, Audiocassette 718_0487)
  Duration: 0:52:56, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times
- Uriya Shavit on Bashar Assad; Steve Block on NJ Public School Lawsuit; June 13 Rally for Quality Public Education; Jonathan Boyarin on the Jewish Community Center (JCC) Panel The Jew and the Camera [2000-25], 2000-06-11; cuid34097 (Box 9, Audiocassette 718_0288)
  Duration: 1:01:35, Preservation Note: Side B is Blank; Program Distorted at Times
  Duplicate of 718_0289, 718_0486
- A: Uriya Shavit on Bashar Assad; Steve Block on NJ Public School Lawsuit; June 13 Rally for Quality Public Education; Jonathan Boyarin on the JCC Panel The Jew and the Camera / B: Gay Pride Show [2000-26], 2000 June 11; 2000 June 25; cuid34098 (Box 9, Audiocassette 718_0289)
  Duration: 2:01:27, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; Channel Imbalance
  Duplicate of 718_0288, 718_0486, 718_0496
- Assad's Death; Rally for Quality Public Education; The Jew and the Camera Panel on Film [2000-050], 2000-06-11; cuid34099 (Box 14, Audiocassette 718_0486)
  Duration: 0:59:59, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times
  Duplicate of 718_0288, 718_0289
- Alternative Jerusalem Day; Police-Out-of-Schools Demonstration; Human Rights Film Festival (Partial) [2000-075], 2000-06-18; cuid34100 (Box 14, Audiocassette 718_0511)
  Duration: 0:55:05
- Gay Pride Show with Melanie Kaye/Kantrowitz, Moisés Kaufman, and Faye Schulman [2000-060], 2000-06-25; cuid34101 (Box 14, Audiocassette 718_0496)
  Duration: 0:59:22, Preservation Note: Digital Errors During Program; Static During Program; Program Distorted at Times; Clicks and Pops During Program
  Duplicate of 718_0289
- Melanie Kaye/Kantrowitz and Maurice Berger on White Lies [2000-072], 2000-07-16; cuid34102 (Box 14, Audiocassette 718_0508)
  Duration: 0:26:47
- A: Martin Duberman on Left Out; Aaron Taub Interview with Edna Nachson on Book Yiddish Proletarian Theatre; Matt Rubin on RNC Protests / B: Igal Sarna on Peace Negotiations Between Israel and Palestine; Jennifer Bleyer and Lori Zimmerman on Philadelphia GOP National Convention Demonstration; Julie Davids and Kai Lumumba-Barrow on Philadelphia Fight on Police [2000-037], 2000 July 30; 2000 August 6; cuid34103 (Box 9, Audiocassette 718_0300)
  Duration: 1:59:48, Preservation Note: Multiple Sections of Silence During Program on Side B; Program Distorted at Times; Static During Program
  Duplicate of 718_0472, 718_0497
- Martin Duberman on Left Out; Aaron Taub Interview with Edna Nachson on Book Yiddish Proletarian Theatre; Matt Rubin on RNC Protests [2000-083-z], 2000-07-30; cuid34104 (Box 13, Audiocassette 718_0472)
  Duration: 0:58:50, Preservation Note: Digital Errors During Program
  Duplicate of 718_0300
- Igal Sarna on Middle East Peace Process; Lori Zimmerman, Julie Davids, and Kai Lumumba-Barrow on Philadelphia Activism [2000-061], 2000-08-06; cuid34105 (Box 14, Audiocassette 718_0497)
  Duration: 0:59:05, Preservation Note: Digital Errors During Program; Program Distorted at Times
- A: Lisa Hostein on Jews in the GOP, Jeremy Burton on the Lieberman VP choice / B: LA DNC Report with Jennifer Bleyer, Steve Rohde, Nan Rubin on Lower East Side synagogues [2000-036], 2000 August 13; 2000 August 20; cuid34106 (Box 9, Audiocassette 718_0299)
  Duration: 1:57:52, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; Channel Imbalance; Static During Program; Brief Speed Fluctuation at End of Side B During Program
  Duplicate of 718_0476, 718_0479, 718_0942
- Lisa Hostein on Jews in GOP; Jeremy Burton on Joseph Lieberman Nomination [2000-043], 2000-08-13; cuid34107 (Box 13, Audiocassette 718_0479)
  Duration: 0:58:01, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times
  Duplicate of 718_0299
- Jennifer Bleyer on DNC in LA; Nan Rubin on Lower East Side Synagogues [2000-040], 2000-08-20; cuid34108 (Box 13, Audiocassette 718_0476)
  Duration: 1:00:02, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; Digital Errors During Program
  Duplicate of 718_0299, 718_0942
- Brooklyn Renaissance Plaza Strike with Carmen Reyes and Juana Mejia, Local 32BJ of SEIU [2000-089-z], 2000-09-01; cuid34109 (Box 21, Reel 718_0942)
  Duration: 0:17:55, Preservation Note: Side B is Blank; Program Distorted at Times; High Background Noise During Program
  Content does not reflect the title; Duplicate of 718_0299, 718_0476
- A: 1st anniversary Gidon Busch killing with Jennifer Bleyer, Phyllis Bennis on Iraq sanctions, On Eagle's Wings conference on Yemenite Jews with Nitza Druyan and Dr. Bernie Kraut / B: NYS Senate race between Roy Goodman and Liz Krueger; Phyllis Bennis on roles of US, UN in Israel/Palestine crisis [2000-033], 2000 August 27; 2000 October 29; cuid34110 (Box 9, Audiocassette 718_0296)
  Duration: 1:59:47, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; Phasing During Program; High Amount of Hum During Program; Static During Program
  Duplicate of 718_0471, 718_0467
- Jennifer Bleyer on Gidone Busch Killing; Phyllis Bennis on 10 Years of Iraq Sanctions; Yemeni Jewish Conference [2000-0832-z], 2000-08-27; cuid34111 (Box 13, Audiocassette 718_0471)
  Duration: 1:02:06, Preservation Note: Digital Errors During Program; Program Distorted at Times
  Duplicate of 718_0296
- Brooklyn Renaissance Plaza Strike with Carmen Reyes and Juana Mejia, Local 32BJ of SEIU [2000-089-z], 2000-09-01; cuid34112 (Box 21, Reel 718_0943)
  Duration: 0:10:17, Preservation Note: Static During Program
  Duplicate of 718_0297, 718_0480
- A: Mike Cinquina, MoMA strike, Jim Bracchitta on SAG strike, Manny Ness on deli organizing effort, Carmen Reyes and Juana Mejia on Brooklyn Renaissance Plaza strike / B: Amira Sohl on Palestinian refugee march, Rachel Bernstein, Harriet Tanzman on Selma vote harassment, Sarah Blustain on Dr. Laura [2000-034], 2000 September 3; 2000 September 10; cuid34113 (Box 9, Audiocassette 718_0297)
  Duration: 1:57:44, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; Phasing During Program; Static During Program
  Duplicate of 718_0480, 718_0943
- Labor Day Show [2000-044], 2000-09-03; cuid34114 (Box 13, Audiocassette 718_0480)
  Duration: 1:03:00, Preservation Note: Digital Errors During Program; Program Distorted at Times
  Duplicate of 718_0297, 718_0943
- Amira Sohl on Palestinian Refugee March; Rachel Bernstein Exhibition; Harriet Tanzman on Corruption and Harassment in Selma Mayoral Race; Sarah Blustain on Dr. Laura Schlessinger [2000-066], 2000-09-10; cuid34115 (Box 14, Audiocassette 718_0502)
  Duration: 0:54:37
  Duplicate of 718_0297
- A: Ellen Willis and Richard Goldstein in the Village Voice on the Gore Nader debate; Sam Day on Mordechai Vanunu / B: Eve Soderman on the new Jewish Museum in Berlin, Egal Ezraty on the Arab-Hebrew Theater of Jaffa, Michael Zweig on "The Working Class Majority" [2000-035], 2000 September 17; 2000 September 24; cuid34116 (Box 9, Audiocassette 718_0298)
  Duration: 1:57:39, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; High Amount of Hiss During Program; Static During Program
  Duplicate of 718_0470, 718_0485
- Eve Soderman on New Jewish Museum in Berlin; Egal Ezraty on the Arab-Hebrew Theatre of Jaffa; Michael Zweig on New Book, The Work Class Majority [2000-035], 2000-09-17; cuid34117 (Box 13, Audiocassette 718_0470)
  Duration: 0:59:52, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times
  Duplicate of 718_0298
- Richard Goldstein and Ellen Willis on Gore vs. Nader; Sam Day on Vanunu Conference [2000-049], 2000-09-24; cuid34118 (Box 14, Audiocassette 718_0485)
  Duration: 0:59:42, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times
- JFREJ Tashlich [2000-091-z], 2000-09-24; cuid34119 (Box 21, Reel 718_0945)
  Duration: 0:16:39, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times
  Duplicate of 718_0294, 718_0469, 718_0129
- Rosh Hashanah Tashlich, Steve Benen on Christian Coalition's Convention, Artist Martha Rosler / B: Palestinian-Israeli blowup, Adam Keller, Nabila Espanioly, Rashid Khalidi [2000-031], 2000-10-01-2000-10-08; cuid34120 (Box 9, Audiocassette 718_0294)
  Duration: 2:03:05, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times
  Duplicate of 718_0469, 718_0945, 718_0941, 718_0129
- JFREJ Activist Tashlich; Christian Coalition Conference; Political Artist, Martha Rosler [2000-081-z], 2000-10-01; cuid34121 (Box 13, Audiocassette 718_0469)
  Duration: 1:03:05, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times
  Duplicate of 718_0945, 718_0294, 718_0129
- Al-Aqsa Intifada Highlights, with Introduction by Adam Keller, Nabila Espanioly, and Rashid Khalidi Introduction, Part 1 [2000-092-z], 2000-10-08; cuid34122 (Box 21, Reel 718_0941)
  Duration: 0:30:08, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; High Background Noise During Program
  Rebroadcast/Duplicate of 718_0294, 718_0129
- Marathon, Side 2 [2000-029], 2000-10-22; cuid34123 (Box 9, Audiocassette 718_0292)
  Duration: 1:01:24, Preservation Note: Side B is Blank; Program Distorted at Times
  Duplicate of 718_0499
- Marathon, Sides 1 and 3 [2000-030], 2000-10-22; cuid34124 (Box 9, Audiocassette 718_0293)
  Duration: 1:38:15, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times
  Duplicate of 718_0498, 718_0500
- Marathon Special with Ruchama Marton and Basya Schechter, Part 1 [2000-062], 2000-10-22; cuid34125 (Box 14, Audiocassette 718_0498)
  Duration: 1:00:43, Preservation Note: Digital Errors During Program
  Duplicate of 718_0293
- Marathon Special with Rashid Khalidi and Frank London, Part 2 [2000-063], 2000-10-22; cuid34126 (Box 14, Audiocassette 718_0499)
  Duration: 1:07:00, Preservation Note: Digital Errors During Program; Program Distorted at Times
  Duplicate of 718_0292
- Marathon Special with Frank London and Michel Warschawski, Part 3 [2000-064], 2000-10-22; cuid34127 (Box 14, Audiocassette 718_0500)
  Duration: 0:37:43, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times
- Liz Krueger and Roy Goodman on NYS Senate Race; Phyllis Bennis on US/UN Role in Israel/Palestine Conflict [2000-079-z], 2000-10-29; cuid34128 (Box 13, Audiocassette 718_0467)
  Duration: 0:59:09, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; Digital Errors During Program
- A: Winona La Dulce, Voice endorses Nader for President, Mideast in Clinton/Lazio race / B: Max Bohmel on Israeli Palestinians, Jews of Morocco with Vivian Mann and Habiba Boumlik [2000-28], 2000 November 5; 2000 November 12; cuid34129 (Box 9, Audiocassette 718_0291)
  Duration: 2:02:35, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; Static During Program
  Duplicate of 718_0477
- Winona LaDuke, Green Party VP Candidate; Gore v. Nader; the Middle East in the Clinton/Lazio Race [2000-042], 2000-11-05; cuid34130 (Box 13, Audiocassette 718_0478)
  Duration: 1:31:59, Preservation Note: Digital Errors During Program; Program Distorted at Times; The Sample Rate of Region 1 is 32kHz; The Sample Rate of Region 2 is 48kHz
  Title does not reflect content; Partial Duplicate of 718_0404, 718_0153, 718_0197
- Alice Shalvi [2000-038], 2000-11-06; cuid34131 (Box 18, Item 718_0657)
- Max Bohnel on Israeli Palestinians; Jews of Morocco with Vivian Mann and Habiba Boumlik [2000-041], 2000-11-12; cuid34132 (Box 13, Audiocassette 718_0477)
  Duration: 1:00:45, Preservation Note: Digital Errors During Program; Static During Program; Program Distorted at Times; Dropouts During Program from 15:44 to 15:50
  Duplicate of 718_0291
- Segev Khalidi [2000-11], 2000-11-18; cuid34133 (Box 8, Audiocassette 718_0274)
  Duration: 1:31:16
  Related to 718_0275, 718_0301
- Segev Khalidi [2000-12], 2000-11-18; cuid34134 (Box 8, Audiocassette 718_0275)
  Duration: 0:19:30, Preservation Note: Side B is Blank
  Related to 718_0274, 718_0301
- A: Jeremy Burton on Election 2000, Dalia Kandiyoti interviews Ammiel Alcalay / B: Rhoda Berenson on Lori Berenson, Karah Newton and Anna Cheung on DKNY protest, Alicia Svigals on "Women in Klezmer and Yiddish Music" [2000-27], 2000 November 19; 2000 November 26; cuid34135 (Box 9, Audiocassette 718_0290)
  Duration: 1:58:23, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; Static During Program
  Duplicate of 718_0473, 718_0474
- Jeremy Burton on Election 2000; Dalia Kandiyoti Interviews Ammiel Alcalay [2000-086-z], 2000-11-19; cuid34136 (Box 13, Audiocassette 718_0473)
  Duration: 1:01:27, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times
  Duplicate of 718_0290, 718_0474
- Rhoda Berenson; DKNY Campaign; Alicia Svigals on Women in Klezmer and Yiddish Music [2000-087-z], 2000-11-26; cuid34137 (Box 13, Audiocassette 718_0474)
  Duration: 0:57:10, Preservation Note: Digital Errors During Program; Digital Dropouts During Program; Program Distorted at Times
  Duplicate of 718_0290, 718_0473
- A: Rashid Khalidi and Tom Segev in conversation / B: Sephardic Film Festival, United Federation of Teachers contract, JFREJ and NYC coalition politics [2000-22], 2000 December 3; 2000 December 10; cuid34138 (Box 9, Audiocassette 718_0285)
  Duration: 1:59:46, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; Static During Program
  Related to 718_0274, 718_0275, 718_0271, 718_0301, 718_0501, 718_0507
- Sephardic Film Festival; United Federation of Teachers (UFT) Contract Negotiations; JFREJ and NYC Coalition Politics [2000-071], 2000-12-03; cuid34139 (Box 14, Audiocassette 718_0507)
  Duration: 1:00:59, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; Digital Errors During Program
  Duplicate of 718_0285
- Rashid Khalidi and Tom Segev [2000-008], 2000-12-10; cuid34140 (Box 8, Audiocassette 718_0271)
  Duration: 0:59:52, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; Side B is Blank; High Amount of Hiss During Program
  Related to 718_0274, 718_0275, 718_0301, 718_0285, 718_0501, 718_0507
- Segev/Khalidi [2000-78], 2000-12-10; cuid34141 (Box 9, Audiocassette 718_0301)
  Duration: 1:34:14, Preservation Note: High Amount of Hiss During Program; Static During Program; Program Distorted at Times
  Related to 718_0274, 718_0275, 718_0271, 718_0501, 718_0285, 718_0507
- Rashid Khalidi and Tom Segev in Public Conversation at Congregation B'nai Jeshurun [2000-065], 2000-12-10; cuid34142 (Box 14, Audiocassette 718_0501)
  Duration: 0:58:17, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times
  Related to 718_0274, 718_0275, 718_0271, 718_0301, 718_0285, 718_0507